Cultural Survival Records MS180
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Indigenous and indigenous issues reference library, 1962 -- 2011; MS180.011; 42.0 Linear Feet
  - UN Declaration on the Rights of Indigenous Peoples and Programme on the Second International Decade of the World's Indigenous People, 2006; MS180.011.057.00040; Tebtebba Foundation; Indigenous Peoples' International Centre for Policy Research and Education (Box 57)
  - UN System Engagement with NGOs, Civil Society, the Private Sector, and Other Actors: A Compendium, 2005; MS180.011.057.00041; United Nations Non-Governmental Liaisons Service (NGLS); German Federal Ministry for Economic Cooperation and Development (Box 57)
  - Uncertain Return: Refugees and Reconciliation in Guatemala, 1989; MS180.011.057.00042; Washington Office on Latin America (Box 57)
  - UNDP World Development Special Report, 1991; MS180.011.057.00043; United Nations Development Program (UNDP) (Box 57)
  - UNEP Directory of Principal Government Bodies Dealing with the Environment, 1988; MS180.011.057.00044; United Environment Programme (UNEP) (Box 57)
  - UNESCO Australia Publications, 1988 -- 1995; MS180.011.057.00045; UNESCO Australia (Box 57)
  - Unews, 1993 -- 1995; MS180.011.057.00046; International Movement Against All Forms of Discrimination and Racism (IMADR) (Box 57)
  - UNHCR Special Report: Refugee Integration, 1984; MS180.011.057.00047; The United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (Box 57)
  - Unidad Alvaro Ulcué, 1988; MS180.011.057.00048; Consejo Regional Indí_gena del Cauca [Regional Indigenous Council of Cauca] (Box 57)
  - Unidad Indígena, 1980 -- 2005; MS180.011.057.00049; Organización Nacional Indígena de Colombia (ONIC) [National Indigenous Organization of Colombia (ONIC)] (Box 57)
    Indigenous Unit
  - Unitar/UNDP Centre on Small Energy Resources Newsletter, 1988 -- 1990; MS180.011.057.00050; United Nations Institute for Training and Research; United Nations Development Programme (Box 57)
  - United Nations Backgrounder, 1996; MS180.011.057.00051; United Nations Department of Public Information (Box 57)
  - United Nations Decade for Women: Equality, Development, and Peace, 1980; MS180.011.057.00052; World Conference of the United Nations Decade for Women: Equality, Development and Peace (Box 57)
  - United Nations Development Education Directory, 1995; MS180.011.057.00053; United Nations Non-Governmental Liaisons Service (NGLS) (Box 57)
  - United Nations Development Programme Publications, 1993; MS180.011.057.00054; United Nations Development Program (UNDP) (Box 57)
  - United Nations Year for Cultural Heritage: Resolution Adopted by the General Assembly of the United Nations, 2003; MS180.011.057.00055; United Nations General Assembly (57th Congress) (Box 57)
  - United Southwestern Lenape Band News, 1992; MS180.011.058.00001 (Box 58)
  - Universal Declaration of Human Rights, 1998; MS180.011.058.00002; United Nations (Box 58)
  - University Research Coordination Office Annual Reports, 1995 -- 1997; MS180.011.058.00003; University Research Coordination Office (Box 58)
  - Unnatural Tragedies of Bangladesh, MS180.011.058.00004; International Movement to Save Bangladesh (Box 58)
  - UNPO News, 1992 -- 2002; MS180.011.058.00005; Unrepresented Nations and Peoples Organization (Box 58)
  - UNSC Resolution 1325: South Asian Women's Perspectives, 2003; MS180.011.058.00006; Gender & Peacebuilding Programme (Box 58)
  - UP Elections: CCHRB Observation Report, 1997; MS180.011.058.00007; Coordinating Council for Human Rights in Bangladesh (Box 58)
  - Up to Date, 1985; MS180.011.058.00008; International Commission of Health Professionals for Health and Human Rights (ICHP) (Box 58)
  - Update, 2002 -- 2010; MS180.011.058.00009; doCip; Indigenous Peoples' Centre for Documentation, Research and Information (Box 58)
  - Update, 1986; MS180.011.058.00010; Task Force on Militarization in Asia and the Pacific (Box 58)
  - Update Latin America, 1982 -- 1987; MS180.011.058.00011; Washington Office on Latin America (Box 58)
  - Update on Law-Related Education, 1998; MS180.011.058.00012; American Bar Association Division for Public Education (Box 58)
  - Urban Forests, 1993; MS180.011.058.00013; American Forestry Association (Box 58)
  - Urgency of Fighting Poverty for Democracy and the Environment, 1993; MS180.011.058.00014; United Nations Non-Governmental Liaison Service (NGLS) (Box 58)
  - Urihi Reports, 1985 -- 1990; MS180.011.058.00015; Commission for the Creation of the Yanomami Park (Box 58)
  - U.S. and Nicaragua: Escalating War? Or Peace?, 1985; MS180.011.058.00016; Nicaragua Peace Project (Box 58)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees Publications, 1982 -- 1999; MS180.011.058.00017; U.S. Committee for Refugees (Box 58)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees Country Reports, 1997 -- 2001; MS180.011.058.00018; U.S. Committee for Refugees (Box 58)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees Issue Papers, 1985 -- 1990; MS180.011.058.00019; U.S. Committee for Refugees (Box 58)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees Issue Papers, 1992 -- 1999; MS180.011.058.00020; U.S. Committee for Refugees (Box 58)
  - U.S. Hands off the Haitian People Newsletter, 1995; MS180.011.058.00021; U.S. Hands off the Haitian People (Box 58)
  - U.S. Initiative Update, 1997 -- 1998; MS180.011.058.00022; Forest Stewardship Council (FSC) (Box 58)
  - U.S. Mab Bulletin, 1994; MS180.011.058.00023; The United States National Committee for the Man and the Biosphere Program (Box 58)
  - U.S. Pirg, 2002; MS180.011.058.00024; The U.S. Public Interest Research Group (Box 58)
  - USTC Newsletter, 1993; MS180.011.058.00025; U.S. Tibet Committee (Box 58)
  - Utopias, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.011.058.00026; Cloudforest Initiatives (Box 58)
  - Vajra Voice, 1990; MS180.011.058.00027; Kunzang Odsal Palyuil Changchub Choling (Box 58)
  - Valhalla Wilderness Society, 1996; MS180.011.058.00028; The Valhalla Wilderness Society (Box 58)
  - Vamos Falar de Índios, 1988 -- 1989; MS180.011.058.00029; FUNAI/SESC (Box 58)
    Let's Talk About Indians
  - Vani News, 1991 -- 1994; MS180.011.058.00030; Voluntary Action Network India (Box 58)
  - Vested Interest, 2001; MS180.011.058.00031; Biodiversity Support Program; World Wildlife Fund (Box 58)
  - Via Fora!, 1983 -- 1996; MS180.011.058.00032; enllaç (Box 58)
  - Vida Silvestre Neotropical, 1989; MS180.011.058.00033; World Wildlife Fund (Box 58)
  - Vida y Libertad, 1989; MS180.011.058.00034; Grupo de Apoyo Mutuo [Mutual Support Group] (Box 58)
    Life and Liberty
  - Video in the Villages II: Utilization of Video-Tapes as an Instrument of Ethnic Affirmation Among Brazilian Indian Groups, 1987; MS180.011.058.00035; Centro de Trabalho Indigenista (CTI) [The Brazilian Indian Work Center] (Box 58)
  - Vierte Welt Aktuell, 1984; MS180.011.058.00036; Gesellschaft für bedrohte Völker [Society for Threatened Peoples] (Box 58)
    Fourth World News
  - Vision Maker, 1998 -- 2005; MS180.011.058.00037; Native American Public Telecommunications (Box 58)
  - Viva Chiapas!, 1994 -- 1995; MS180.011.058.00038; Conversion for Reclaiming Earth in the Americas (Box 58)
    Live Chiapas!
  - Viva Zapata: Generation, Gender, and Historical Consciouness in the Reception of Ejido Reform in Oaxaca, 1994; MS180.011.058.00039; Center for U.S.-Mexican Studies - University of California, San Diego (Box 58)
  - Voices from the Earth, 2000 -- 2010; MS180.011.058.00040; Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 58)
  - Vo'ne Jchonolajeletik Ta Tzinakanta: Los Antiguos Comerciantes Zinacantecos, 1991; MS180.011.058.00041; Sna Jtz'ibajom [The House of the Writer]; Casa de los Escritores Cultura de los Indios Mayas, A.C. [House of Writers Mayan Indian Culture] (Box 58)
  - Vrijbuiter!, 1998; MS180.011.058.00042; VZW De Vrijbuiter [Association Freebooter] (Box 58)
    Filibuster!
  - W.I.L.D.C.A.T., 1993; MS180.011.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - Wadrihwa, 1989; MS180.011.059.00002; Woodland Cultural Centre (Box 59)
  - Waldhaansso: Journal of the Union of Oromo Students in North America, 1981 -- 1988; MS180.011.059.00003; Union of Oromo Students in North America (Box 59)
  - WAPA: Washington Association of Professional Anthropologists, 1985; MS180.011.059.00004; Washington Association of Professional Anthropologists (Box 59)
  - War & Peace Digest, 1994 -- 2002; MS180.011.059.00005; War & Peace Foundation (Box 59)
  - War in the Gulf: An Environmental Perspective, 1991; MS180.011.059.00006; Political Ecology Group-PEG (Box 59)
  - Washington Watch: A Private Newsletter, 1972 -- 1973; MS180.011.059.00007; Tristram Coffin (Box 59)
  - Washington's Indians, 1985; MS180.011.059.00008; Seattle Times Special Reprint (Box 59)
  - Watershed, 1993 -- 1994; MS180.011.059.00009; Carrier Sekani Tribal Council (Box 59)
  - Watershed: People's Forum on Ecology (Folder 1 of 6), 1995 -- 1996; MS180.011.059.00010; Towards Ecological Recovery and Regional Alliance (Box 59)
  - Watershed: People's Forum on Ecology (Folder 2 of 6), 1996 -- 1997; MS180.011.059.00011; Towards Ecological Recovery and Regional Alliance (Box 59)
  - Watershed: People's Forum on Ecology (Folder 3 of 6), 1997 -- 1998; MS180.011.059.00012; Towards Ecological Recovery and Regional Alliance (Box 59)
  - Watershed: People's Forum on Ecology (Folder 4 of 6), 1998; MS180.011.059.00013; Towards Ecological Recovery and Regional Alliance (Box 59)
  - Watershed: People's Forum on Ecology (Folder 5 of 6), 1999 -- 2000; MS180.011.059.00014; Towards Ecological Recovery and Regional Alliance (Box 59)
  - Watershed: People's Forum on Ecology (Folder 6 of 6), 2000 -- 2001; MS180.011.059.00015; Towards Ecological Recovery and Regional Alliance (Box 59)
  - We Continue Forever: Sorrow and Strength of Guatemalan Women, 1983; MS180.011.059.00016; Women's International Resource Exchange (Box 59)
  - We Speak for Ourselves: Population and Development, 1994; MS180.011.059.00017; The Panos Institute (Box 59)
  - We: A Magazine about Us, 1999; MS180.011.059.00018; GCC Associates (Box 59)
  - Wedline: Newsletter on Women, Environment, and Sustainable Development, 1995 -- 1996; MS180.011.059.00019; Environmental Liaison Centre International (Box 59)
  - West Papua Information Kit, 1995; MS180.011.059.00020; Australia West Papua Association, Sydney (Box 59)
  - Western Canada Wilderness Committee Educational Report, 1991; MS180.011.059.00021; The Wild Campaign Western Canada (Box 59)
  - Western Shoshone Defense Project Newsletter, 1993; MS180.011.059.00022; Western Shoshone Defense Project (Box 59)
  - What They Say, 1995; MS180.011.059.00023; Rural Litigation and Entitlement Kendra (Box 59)
  - What, Then Is the American, This New Man?, 1998; MS180.011.059.00024; Center for Immigration Studies (Box 59)
  - When the Iron Bird Flies: A Handbook on Tibetan Cultural Survival, 1995; MS180.011.059.00025; Tibet Education Network and the Milarepa Fund (Box 59)
  - Whispers in the Dust: A Moche Mystery Story, 1993; MS180.011.059.00026; Smiley Karst (Box 59)
  - Who Owns Nature? Indigenous Peoples and Democracy, 1996; MS180.011.059.00027; The Fourth World Association of Sweden (Box 59)
  - Wholesale Destruction: The SLORC/SPDC Campaign to Obliterate All Hill Villages in Papun and Eastern Nyaunglebin Districts, 1998; MS180.011.059.00028; Karen Human Rights Group (Box 59)
  - Why Somalis Flee, 1989; MS180.011.059.00029; Department of State, Bureau for Refugee Programs (Box 59)
  - WILDAF News, 1993; MS180.011.059.00030; Women in Law and Development in Africa (Box 59)
  - Wilderness Committee Educational Report, 1997; MS180.011.059.00031; Wilderness Committee; Raincoast Conservation Society (Box 59)
  - Wildlife Damage Review, 1991; MS180.011.059.00032 (Box 59)
  - Wilson Quarterly, 1998; MS180.011.059.00033; Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Box 59)
  - Winter in Beijing: Continuing Repression Since the Beijing Massacre, 1990; MS180.011.059.00034; International League for Human Rights; Ad Hoc Study Group on Human Rights in China (Box 59)
  - Witness for Peace Newsletter, 1992; MS180.011.059.00035; Witness for Peace (Box 59)
  - Wolf Howls: The Tsilhqot'in Nation Journal, 1999; MS180.011.059.00036; The Wild Horse Wise Outfit Consulting and Media Production Co.; Tsilhqot'in National Government (Box 59)
  - WomaNews: N.Y.C. Feminist Newspaper and Calendar of Events, 1988; MS180.011.059.00037; Womanews (Box 59)
  - Women and Education, 1980; MS180.011.059.00038; Ministry of Education for Denmark (Box 59)
  - Women and Global Corporations: Work, Roles, Resistance, 1982; MS180.011.059.00039; American Friends Service Committee (Box 59)
  - Women and the New International Economic Order, 1989; MS180.011.059.00040; United Nations Development Programme Division of Information (Box 59)
  - Women Ending Hunger, 1985; MS180.011.059.00041; The Hunger Project (Box 59)
  - Women Envision, 1994 -- 1998; MS180.011.059.00042; Isis International Media (Box 59)
  - Women in Action (Folder 1 of 5), 1991 -- 1994; MS180.011.059.00043; Isis International Media (Box 59)
  - Women in Action (Folder 2 of 5), 1991 -- 1997; MS180.011.059.00044; Isis International Media (Box 59)
  - Women in Action (Folder 3 of 5), 1998 -- 2000; MS180.011.059.00045; Isis International Media (Box 59)
  - Women in Action (Folder 4 of 5), 1999 -- 2003; MS180.011.059.00046; Isis International Media (Box 59)
  - Women in Action (Folder 5 of 5), 1998 -- 2007; MS180.011.059.00047; Isis International Media (Box 59)
  - Women in the GDR, 1980; MS180.011.059.00048; Council of Ministers of the German Democratic Republic (Box 59)
  - Women in the Third World: Harvard Development Forum, 1989; MS180.011.059.00049; The Harvard Development Forum (Box 59)
  - Women of Europe, 1980; MS180.011.059.00050; Commission of the European Committees (Box 59)
  - Women of the World, 1980; MS180.011.059.00051; Equal Times Inc. (Box 59)
  - Women's Health Collection: Latin American and Caribbean Women's Health Network, 2006; MS180.011.059.00052; Latin American and Caribbean Women's Health Network (Box 59)
  - Women's Health Exchange, 1998 -- 2001; MS180.011.059.00053; Hesperian Foundation (Box 59)
  - Women's Health Journal, 2005 -- 2006; MS180.011.060.00001; Latin American and Caribbean Women's Health Network (Box 60)
  - Women's Initiation to Fight Against Victimization of Women, 1993; MS180.011.060.00002; Informal Sector Service Centre (INSEC) (Box 60)
  - Women's Participation in Decision Making Porcesses, MS180.011.060.00003; Danish Women's Society (Box 60)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1980; MS180.011.060.00004; The Feminist Press; The Natinoal Women's Studies Association (Box 60)
  - Women's Views on the Earth Charter, 1997; MS180.011.060.00005; Boston Research Center for the 21st Century (Box 60)
  - Women's Watch, 1986 -- 1991; MS180.011.060.00006; International Women's Rights Action Watch (Box 60)
  - Women's Work, 1993; MS180.011.060.00007 (Box 60)
  - Women's Work, 1984; MS180.011.060.00008; The Society for Folk Arts Preservation, Inc. (Box 60)
  - Women's World Summit Foundation, 1991; MS180.011.060.00009 (Box 60)
  - Work and the Worker in Islam, 1980; MS180.011.060.00010; The Hamdami Foundation (Box 60)
  - Worker Rights News, 1993; MS180.011.060.00011; International Labor Rights Education & Research Fund (Box 60)
  - Working in the Zone, 1992; MS180.011.060.00012; Asian Human Rights Commission (Box 60)
  - Working Papers on South American Indians, 1979 -- 1980; MS180.011.060.00013; Bennington College (Box 60)
  - Working Peoples' News, 1993; MS180.011.060.00014; The Working People's News (Box 60)
  - World Council of Indigenous Peoples Newsletter, 1983 -- 1991; MS180.011.060.00015; World Council of Indigenous Peoples (Box 60)
  - World Court Project Report 3, 1993; MS180.011.060.00016; World Court Project (Box 60)
  - World Democracy News, 1989; MS180.011.060.00017; World Democracy News Corporation (Box 60)
  - World Development Forum, 1984; MS180.011.060.00018; The Hunger Project (Box 60)
  - World Health Organization Publications, 1985 -- 1989; MS180.011.060.00019; World Health Organization (Box 60)
  - World Heritage Newsletter, 2005; MS180.011.060.00020; Unesco (Box 60)
  - World Military and Social Expenditures, 1991; MS180.011.060.00021; World Priorities (Box 60)
  - World Rainforest Report, 1990 -- 1994; MS180.011.060.00022; Rainforest Action Network (Box 60)
  - World Rivers Review, 1991 -- 1999; MS180.011.060.00023; International Rivers Network (Box 60)
  - World Uranium Hearing: Uranium Mining, Atomic Bomb Testing, Nuclear Waste Storage: A Global Survey, 1992; MS180.011.060.00024; The World Uranium Hearing (Box 60)
  - World Watch, 2003; MS180.011.060.00025; Worldwatch Institute (Box 60)
  - World Watch Papers, 1993 -- 1994; MS180.011.060.00026; Worldwatch Institute (Box 60)
  - World Water, 1982 -- 1983; MS180.011.060.00027; Thomas Telford, Ltd. (Box 60)
  - World Wide, 2002 -- 2004; MS180.011.060.00028; Netherlands Organization for International Cooperation in Higher Education (Box 60)
  - World Wise, 1992; MS180.011.060.00029; South-North News Service, Inc. (Box 60)
  - WorldPaper, 1979 -- 1990; MS180.011.060.00030; World Times Inc. (Box 60)
  - WorldViews, 1997; MS180.011.060.00031 (Box 60)
  - WorldWIDE News, 1994; MS180.011.060.00032; WorldWIDE (Box 60)
  - WRI Ideas and Issues, 1992 -- 1997; MS180.011.060.00033; World Resources Institute (Box 60)
  - Yachay Wasi 'Simin', 1996 -- 2010; MS180.011.060.00034; Yachay Wasi, Inc. (Box 60)
  - Yakama Nation Review, 1998 -- 2003; MS180.011.060.00035 (Box 60)
  - Yanomami: A Todos os Povos da Terra, 1990; MS180.011.060.00036; Ação Pela Cidadania [Action for Citizenship] (Box 60)
    Yanomami: A Todos os Povos da Terra
  - Yellow Springs Review, 1990; MS180.011.060.00037; Yellow Springs Institute (Box 60)
  - Yes!, 2009; MS180.011.060.00038; Positive Futures Network (Box 60)
  - You Have a Right To Know, 2003; MS180.011.060.00039; International You Have a Right To Know (Box 60)
  - Youth, 1982 -- 1983; MS180.011.060.00040; WCC Youth Office Education and Renewal Unit (Box 60)
  - Zalacaín, 2002; MS180.011.060.00041; Harvard University (Box 60)
  - Zeitschrift für Kulturaustausch, 1994 -- 1995; MS180.011.060.00042; Institut für Auslandsbeziehungen Stuttgart [Institute for Foreign Cultural Relations in Stuttgart] (Box 60)
    Journal from Cultural Exchange
  - Zelaya Norte Zona Especial 1, 1983; MS180.011.060.00043; Centro de Comunicación Internacional [International Communication Center] (Box 60)
    North Zelaya Special Zone 1
  - Zimbabwe Women's Resource Center & Network News Bulletin, 1993; MS180.011.060.00044; Zimbabwe Women's Resource Center & Network (Box 60)
- Additional accessions, 1990 -- 2010; MS180.012; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Ted Macdonald digital files from laptop, 2004 -- 2009; MS180-001
  - Content from multiple removable media taken out during rehousing, 1990 -- 2010; MS180-002
  - Cultural Survival digital files, 1990 -- 2010; MS180-003
    112 transfer bags containing digital files transferred from 3.5" floppy disks, zip disks, CDs, and DVDs using Bagger.
  - Cultural Survival digital files, 1990 -- 2010; MS180-004
    87 transfer bags containing digital files transferred from 3.5" floppy disks, zip disks, CDs, and DVDs using Bagger.
  - Cultural Survival digital media, 1990 -- 2010; MS180-005 (Box 1)
    Box contains 3.5" floppies and zip disks yet to be stabilized and a few already-stabilized audio CDs.
- Website, 2013 -- 2019; MS180.005368; 1 Web sites
  This series is open for research.
  Website crawled by DCA to document the presence of Cultural Survival on the web. The website in this series is crawled on an annual basis.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Archived websites can be viewed online using the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine.
  - Cultural Survival | Partnering with Indigenous Peoples to Defend their Lands, Languages, and Cultures, 2013-02-16 -- 2019-09-17; MS180.005369; 1 Web sites